내게 말해보게, 아케이디,
HETTY:
Tell me, Arkady,
왜 그들은 당신이 죽길 바라나?
why do they want you dead?
왜냐하면 내가 그들의 배를
돌려주지 않으려고 하기 때문이오
Because I would not give
them their ship back.
배엔 뭐가 실렸지?
What was on the boat?
전세계 어디서 나 통용되는
유일한 진짜 화폐
The only true currency accepted
everywhere in the world.
석유로 군
Oil.
1억 달라 이상이요
More than $100 million.
그 정도면 충분한
전쟁자금이 되겠네
That's enough to finance a war.
한 가지 더 물어보죠
CALLEN:
One more question.
애나는 누구죠?
Who's Anna?
괜찮은 러시아 아가씨지
Nice Russian girl.
유조선 건은
무슨 진척 없나?
Any update on
the oil tanker?
네, 거기 없더라 구요
Yeah, it's not there.
기상 위성이
찾지를 못했어요
Weather satellite
couldn't find it.
그리고 그 자동응답기는
꺼져 버렸고요
And the ship's transponder's
been turned off.
사실 내 육감으로는,
이 일이 아직
끝나지 않은 것 같다네
I have a hunch this one
isn't quite over with.
(laughter,
dance music pulsating)
좋아, 아가씨들, 좋아요
PHOTOGRAPHER:
Love it, ladies, love it!
아름다워
(whoops)
Oh, beautiful.
좀 더
Work for it.
열정적으로, 아가씨들
Show me you
want it, baby.
열정적으로, 그렇지
Show me
you want it-- yes!
좋아, 아주 좋아
Love it, love it.
그거야
Yes.
좋아!
아름다워!
Love it! Beautiful!
좋아
Love it.
훌륭해, 아가씨들
Wonderful, ladies.
훌륭하다고!
Wonderful!
이제...
파도 속으로, 아가씨들
Now...
into the surf, ladies.
좋았어!
물로 들어가!
Love it!
Get in the water!
파티 합시다!
오, 당신들 정말 좋아!
Let's party!
Oh, I love you!
Ay, yi, yi!
뭐가 문제지, 렉시?
What's the problem
now, Lexi?
난.. 못해요, 세바스찬
I-I can't, Sebastian.
음악 꺼!
Turn the music off!
이리와, 렉시, 물에 들어 와
네가 다 망치고 있잖아
Come on, Lexi, get into the water.
You're blowing it.
내가 어렸을 때
물에 빠져 죽을뻔 했어
I almost drowned as a kid.
바다 공포증이 있다고
I got a thing about the ocean.
그건 말도 안 되잖아
That doesn't even make sense.
넌 수영복 모델이라고
You are a swimsuit model.
싫으면 말던가
Or at least you were.
렉시...
Lexi...
넌 특별난 게 없어
you are not special,
내 시간만 허비하게 한다고
but you are
wasting my time.
이제 물로 당장 들어 오든지
아니면 여기서 꺼지라고!
Now get your ass into
this water, or get off my set!
물속엔 아무것도 없단...
There is nothing
in this water that could...
Aah! Aah! Oh!
(yells)
(screams)
(screaming)
(all screaming, shrieking)
♪ NCIS: LA 6x23 ♪
Kolcheck, A.
방송일: 2015년 5월 11일
NCIS: LA 6x23
Kolcheck, A.
Original Air Date on May 11, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
번역 및 싱크 재조정: 비키남
난 당최 이해가 안돼
I just don't get it.
명백히, 넌 우정의
개념에 대해서 모르고 있어
Clearly, you don't understand
the concept of friendship.
난 네가 마치
현금인출기 같다고
I'm the friend
telling you
말해 줄 수 있는
친구라고
you're being used
as an ATM machine.
이번엔 또 뭔데?
I mean, what is
it for this time?
부동산?
발명품?
Real estate? An invention?
다단계 사기?
A Ponzi scheme?
(Kensi chuckles)
너도 그게 뭔지
모르는구나, 그렇지?
You don't know, do you?
여러분, 저 좀 도와줘요
만일 여러분들의 친구가
Gentlemen, help me out--
if you have a good friend
곤경에 처해서
돈을 빌려달라고 한다면
어떻게 하시겠어요?
that's in a jam and needs
a loan, what do you do?
아니, 아니
모든 걸 다 얘기 해야지
KENSI: No, no, no, don't
withhold information.
그 친구는 아직
갚지 않은
This friend has had
several loans
대출이
여러 건 있어요
which he has not
paid back.
'여러 건'이면
정확히 몇 개?
How many is "several"?
- 3 개
- 몇 개?
Three.
How many?
5 개
Five.
몇 개라고?
What was that?
- 7 개
- 그럼 그렇지
Seven.
Aha, there it is.
만일 나라면, 그 친구한테
'은행 문 닫았어'라고 할꺼야
If it were me, I'd tell him
the bank is closed.
어디에 쓸
돈인지에 따라 다르지
It depends
what it's for.
나라면 사전에
계약서를 써서
But I would establish terms
up front
서로 스트레스 받을 일
없도록 할꺼야
so there's no pressure
on either of us.
하지만 뭐든 절대로
돌려 받을 거라 기대하고
But you should never
lend anything
that you actually expect
to get back.
빌려 주지는 말라고
뭔가 있었구나?
What was that?
그래, 그게 뭐죠?
Yeah, what was that?
- 있긴 뭐가?
- 그래 보여
What was what?
CALLEN: That look.
그거 나보고
한 말이야?
Was that directed at me?
네가 꺼냈으니
하는 말인데,
Well, since you
brought it up.
내 야시경 고글,
내 경찰봉,
My night vision goggles,
my stun baton,
내 새 헤드폰...
my new headphones...
너도 그것들 전부 멕시코에서
날아가 버린거 알잖아
You know those got blown up
in Mexico.
네가 빌려 갔지
그러니 네 책임 이잖아
You borrowed them.
They're your responsibility...
- 내 말 알겠지?
- 매우 어렵네요
You see what I'm saying.
Very difficult.
'빌려준 거'랑
'선물로 준 거'는 다르다고
SAM: That's why it's called
"borrowing" and not a gift.
사건입니다, 형님들
(whistles)
We got a case, boys.
그리고 누님
And girl.
고맙네요
Thank you.
내 빈티지 롤렉스
My vintage Rolex.
그걸 돌려 받고 싶다고?
You wanted that back?
내가 왜 안그러겠어?
Why wouldn't I
want it back?
오랜 된거 잖아
It's old.
빈티지라고
It's vintage.
딕스, 딕스
Deeks, Deeks.
DEEKS: Yeah.
혹.. 혹시, 어
Uh, d-did you, uh...
새 어플 사업 계획서
읽어 봤어?
did you check out the
business plan for my new app?
엄청나게 잘 될거라구
I mean, come on,
it's gonna be huge.
응, 아니, 그 건은 말이야,
난 못 하겠어, 친구
Yeah, no, about that,
I-I can't do it, buddy.
자넨 지난 8건의 대출도
아직 안 갚았잖아
You haven't paid back the last
eight outstanding loans.
- 대출이라고?
- 응, 대출
Loans?
Loans.
그건 주식 투자지
Those were equity
investments.
아시겠죠, 동업자님?
Right, partner?
이봐, 이런 말도 있잖아,
Come on,
whatever happened
'실패는 성공의 어머니다'
to "if we're not failing,
we're not trying," huh?
그래, 알아, 훌륭한 말이지
Yeah, I know,
that sounds fantastic.
난 그냥... 못 하겠다고
I just, I can't...
I can't do it.
미안해
Sorry.
주식 가치가 곧
더 올라갈 텐데?
Equity's only gonna
get more expensive.
후회 할거야
You're gonna regret this.
이미 하고 있다고
I already do.
뭐지?
What?
오늘아침 롱비치로
밀려 온 시체입니다
This body washed up
in Long Beach this morning.
두 손은 묶였고, 가슴에
두군데 총상이 있습니다
Hands bound,
two gunshots to the chest.
해안 경비대가
2 마일 떨어진 해안에서
Coast Guard found three more
bodies just like this
이와 똑 같은 시신
3 구를 더 발견 했답니다
two miles off the coast,
same scenario.
처형을 당했군
They were executed.
그들이 누군지 아나?
Any idea who they are?
아케이디의 실종 된
유조선 기억하시나요?
Remember Arkady's
missing oil tanker?
그 배의 선원들 입니다
This is the crew.
그 중 일부 선원들이죠
Well, part of it.
그럼 유조선이
발견 된건가?
So the tanker's been recovered.
아뇨, 시체들만
No, just the bodies.
그렇다면 배에서
폭동이 일어났거나
So there was either
a mutiny on board,
외부의 누군가가
그 배를 장악했다는 얘기군
or someone outside took control
of the ship.
그 유조선은 1억달라 이상의
석유를 싣고있죠
That tanker's carrying
over $100 million in oil.
누군든 그걸 훔치면
현금으로 바꾸려고 하겠군
Whoever stole it wants
to convert it into cash.
아니면 항구로 들어와...
Or sail it into the harbor...
폭파 시키든지
and boom.
지난번 아케이디와
계약이 깨진 남매 있었지?
Brother and sister that
brokered the deal with Arkady?
패트릭과 엘리야 버클리?
Yeah, Patrick and Elia Berkeley?
패트릭은 판결을
받을 때 까지
Patrick is being held
빅터빌 형무소에
구금 되 있습니다
until sentencing at
Victorville Penitentiary.
그는 미국의 대 러시아
경제 제재 조치를
He's charged with
circumventing
교묘히 우회한 죄목으로
기소 되었습니다.
U.S. economic sanctions
against Russia.
그 누이는 어디있지?
시내에?
Okay, what about the sister?
Metro?
리돈도에 있습니다
Redondo.
집에서 편히 지내고 있죠
Comfort of
her own home.
계약은 그녀가 했고
She did a deal.
나머지 일은 모두
남동생에게 시켰습니다
Pinned the entire operation
on her brother.
Wow.
기름이 피보다 진하군
Turns out oil's thicker
than blood.
아케이디는
어떻게 됐지?
What about Arkady?
그에게 추적장치를
달았었나?
We got a bead on him?
헤티가 그의 차에 부착한
추적장치의 신호로는
Uh, well, the trackers
that Hetty had installed
on his cars indicate
that he's at home.
그가 집에 있다고
나옵니다
시체가 아직
부패하지 않은 것으로 보아
Well, the bodies aren't
decomposed, yet,
so the ship could still be
in the area.
배가 아직 근처에
있을지도 몰라
모든 지역을
다 살펴 봤지만
We've looked
everywhere.
건초더미에서
바늘찾기 더라구요
It's like trying to find
a needle in a haystack.
자네들이
버클리 남매를 맡아
You guys handle
the Berkeleys.
패트릭부터 시작해
그의 누이가 그를 배신했으니
Start with Patrick,
his sister double-crossed him--
그가 실토를 한다고 해도
잃을 건 없을거야
he's got nothing to
lose by speaking.
알았습니다
All right.
어려울거네
Might be difficult.
패트릭 버클리가
오늘아침 피살 당했어
Patrick Berkeley was murdered
this morning.
엘리야만으로
시작할 수 밖에 없네
You're gonna have
to start with Elia.
나쁜 소식을 전하러
가야겠군요
Better go deliver the bad news.
이 일과 관련 있다고
보십니까?
Think it's related?
뭐 단순한 감옥 사고라고
볼 수도 있겠고
Well, it could be just
a prison incident,
아니면 그이상 뭔가
있을지도 모르지
or it could be more.
어찌 됐건
What I do know is
그 유조선을 다시 한번
잘 찾아 봐야 만 할걸세
we got a second shot
at finding that oil tanker.
시간 낭비하지 말고
Don't waste it.
결국 또 자네와 나, 그리고
그 인기만점 러시아사람이 엮였구만
You know, that leaves you, me
and your favorite Russian.
왜, 자네 그사람
좋아 하잖아
Come on, you like him.
아주 약간
A little.
그래, 수고들 해
SAM:
Yeah, keep it up.
약간만요?
Little bit?
이상하게 조용하네
Awfully quiet.
경비원들은 어디갔지?
Where are the guards?
차들은 여기 있네
Cars are here.
그래도 뭔가 이상해
Still doesn't feel right.
뭐 하는거야?
What are you doing?
그는 자기 차에
폭파장치를 한 사람이야
He rigged his car to explode.
What do you think
he'll do to his house?
자기 집은 어떻게
해 놨을 것 같아?
내가 만일 아케이디의
과대망상 때문에 죽는다면
If I die because of
Arkady's paranoia,
그건 할 수 없지 뭐
I deserve it.
(chuckles)
저 안으로
들어가 봐야 겠네
We got to get
in there.
부엌 바닥에
피가 흘러있는 것 같아
Could be bleeding out
on the kitchen floor.
나한테 점검 해
보라지도 않네?
You don't want me
to check it?
자네 그 모험심은
어디갔나?
Where's your sense
of adventure?
이 속에 잘 있지
It's in here.
단지 여기 문앞을 난장판으로
만들고 싶지 않을 뿐이야
I just don't want it to splatter
all over the driveway.
Uh-huh.
됐지?
Good?
확인 끝
Clear.
집에 아무도 없군
It's all clear.
아케이디가
석유를 중계했다면
If Arkady brokered
the deal for the oil,
여기 어딘가에
흔적이 있을거야
there's got to be something
here to lead us to it.
(chuckles)
인상적이군
Impressive.
뭘 찾았어?
You got something?
카메라야, 웃어봐
Smile for the camera.
그가 과대망상인게
다행이군
It's a good thing he's paranoid.
도대체 저기다
뭘 넣어 둔거지?
SAM: The hell has
he got in there,
클렘린 궁
설계도라도 들었나?
blueprints to
the Kremlin?
1-1-3-1
1-1-3-1.
여권을 꺼냈어
CALLEN:
He took his passport.
급히 도망가고 있군
He's skipping town.
왜 택시를 타지?
SAM:
Why take a taxi?
헤티가 추적하는걸
아는 걸까?
Think he knows
Hetty's tracking him?
(phone line ringing)
- 캘런 선배
- 에릭
Hey, Callan.
Eric.
- 무슨 일이죠?
- 뭐 알아낸 거 없나?
Hey, what's up?
What do you got?
아케이디가 약 두시간 전에
택시를 타고 갔네
Arkady got a taxi
about two hours ago.
어디서 내렸는지
좀 알아 봐
See if you can find out where
they dropped him off.
알았습니다
On it.
Yeah.
분명히 뭔가에
겁을 먹은 것 같아
Well, something definitely
has him freaked out.
여기 감시 영상이 들어있는
하드 디스크도 지우지 않았어
He didn't wipe the hard drive
on his security camera here.
SAM:
Gotcha.
찾았다
이거 봐
SAM: This guy.
(keypad beeping)
서류들, 여권들...
Documents, passports...
별게 다 들어 있군
This could be anything.
그거 레즈니코프인가?
SAM:
Is that Resnikov?
그의 실제 이름은
한스 슈라이버야
His real name is
Hans Schrieber.
내가 얘기 했지
Huh.
Like I told you.
복잡하다고
It's complicated.
자네 아버지가 러시아를
탈출하는 사람들을 도왔군
So your old man helped people
escape from Russia.
그래
Yeah.
그것 때문에 아버지를
강제 노동 수용소에 보냈어
They sent him
to the Gulag for that.
답을 찾는 이가
나 뿐만이 아닌 것 같네
Guess I'm not the only one
looking for answers.
자네 아버지가
영웅이라 좋겠네
It's pretty cool,
your dad being a hero.
솔직히 인정해야지
You got it honest.
그게 뭐야?
What you got?
모르겠어
I'm not sure.
석유 관련 단서는
여기 없네
There's nothing in here
to lead us to the oil.
여기서 나가자
Let's get out of here.
아케이디가 지금 우릴
비웃고 있을지도 몰라
Arkady could be laughing
at us right now.
엘리야가 아직도
전화를 안 받고 있어
DEEKS: Elia's still not
picking up her phone.
그러니까, 버클리 남매가
가업을 이어 받아
So the Berkeleys inherit
the family business,
거의 망해 가더니, 결국
경제 제재 조치 위반까지
저지르게 된거야
they run it into the ground
and end up economic sanctions.
가파른 내리막이군
Slippery slope.
Yeah.
문제는, 어째서 엘리야가
자기 남동생에게 불리한
증언을 했느냐는 거지
Question is-- why would Elia
testify against her own brother?
너는 그들이 서로
친했다고 가정하고 있잖아
Well, you're assuming
they liked each other.
둘이 사업을
같이 할 정도로는 친했지
(knocks on door) Well, enough to go
into business together.
어쩌면 동생이 누나한테
불리한 증언을 하라고 했는지도 몰라
Or maybe he told her
to testify against him
자기 누나를 보호하려고 말이야,
무슨 얘긴지 알지?
to save her,
you know what I mean?
Like a, like a personal
sacrifice; an act of love.
사랑에서 우러난
개인적 희생이라고나 할까?
그들이 부부사이라면 모를까
Yeah, I would get that
between a husband and a wife,
남매 지간에?
but a brother and sister?
(knocking)
어쩌면 둘 다 인지도...
Maybe they're both.
Ew!
What?
- 말 되잖아
- 그건 말도 안돼
It makes sense.
Nothing you say makes sense.
이렇게 생각해 봐
Think about this.
이 전체 범죄 왕국이,
금지된 욕망에 대한
This whole criminal empire
is spawned
뒤틀린 좌절감으로부터
잉태 되었다고 말이야
from the twisted frustration
of forbidden lust.
와우
Wow.
그럴듯 해, '섬뜩'씨
Thank you for that, Mr. Creepy.
말이 되잖아!
That makes sense!
내 말 뜻 몰라?
그녀가 증언을 했다고
You know what I mean?
She testified.
좋아, 둘 중 하나라도 감옥에
안 가려고 그랬다는 건 인정할께
Okay, I'll give you they don't
both have to go to prison.
Especially if they have business
on the outside.
특히 그들이 밖에서 하는
사업이 있다면 말이지
맞아
Right.
이를테면 1억 달라짜리
유조선 같은 거
Like a hundred-million-dollar
oil tanker.
이건 금지된 욕망의 힘이야
This is the power
of forbidden lust.
딕스...
Deeks...
셋, 둘, 하나...
Three, two, one...
(Deeks exhales)
켄지?
Kens?
(sighs)
우리가 너무 늦었어
We're too late.
누군가가 엘리야와 그녀의
남동생을 제거하고 싶어했군
So somebody wanted Elia and
her brother out of the way.
문제는 그게
누구냐 하는거지
고마워요 스티브,
감사합니다.
DEEKS:
Thank you, Steve. Appreciate it.
별 말씀을
STEVE:
You got it.
유조선 선원들을
살해한 방법과
DEEKS:
Well, the method is consistent
동일한 방법으로
살해 됐어
with the way
the oil tanker crew was killed.
누군가 그녀를 죽이려는 게
이번이 두 번째야
This is the second time
somebody's tried to kill her.
이번엔 운이 없었네
This time?
Not so lucky.
몇주전 아케이디를
죽이려 했던
What about the hit man
그 암살범은
어떻게 됐지?
from the Arkady sting
a few weeks ago?
니콜라이 브랜토프
DEEKS:
Nicolai Brantov.
캘런은 그가 러시아를 위해
일 한다고 생각했어
Yeah, Callen thought he was
working for the Russians.
그가 누굴 위해
일 하던 간에
Well, whoever
he was working for,
짐싸서 집에 간 게
아닌 건 확실 해
they obviously haven't
packed up and gone home.
(phone line ringing)
켄지 선배,
무슨일 있나요?
NELL: Kensi, what's
happening with you guys?
넬, 니콜라이 브랜토프가
Hey, Nell.
Can you find out
exactly who Nikolai Brantov
was working for?
정확히 누굴 위해
일 하는지 좀 알아 봐 줄래?
- 네 알겠어요
- 그래 고마워
Yeah, no problem.
Great, thank you.
내 장담하는데,
그가 누가 됐던
Yeah, I bet money
whoever that is...
분명 유조선을
가진 사람 일꺼야
has the oil tanker.
샷건이다!
Shotgun!
잡았다
Gotcha.
유조선을 찾았나?
Did you find the tanker?
아직 아닙니다
Not yet.
깃발을 계속
달지 않았다면
If it's been unflagged,
가능도 했겠지만...
it might be possible, but...
만화경이 아케이디의
택시를 찾았습니다
Kaleidoscope
found Arkady's taxi.
어디서?
GRANGER:
Where?
스튜디오 시티의 한 주차장에
그를 내려 줬습니다
ERIC: Dropped him off
at a garage in Studio City.
아케이디가 들어가고...
Arkady enters...
그리고 나서 4분 뒤에...
And then,
four minutes later...
다스비다냐
(러시아어로 '잘 가세요')
Dasvidaniya, baby.
어떤 사람들은
대포폰을 숨겨 두는데
Some guys stash burn phones,
아케이디는 대포차를
숨겨 두는군
Arkady stashes burn vehicles.
저 차들에 전부
보험을 들려면
Yeah. Insurance on
all those extra cars
분명 보통일이
아니겠는데
must be a nightmare.
(chuckles)
그가 지금은 어디있나?
Where is he now?
Uh...
벤츄라 대로를 타고
서쪽으로 갔습니다.
headed west
on Ventura Boulevard.
그 정보를
캘런과 샘에게 알리게
GRANGER: All right, get that Intel
to Callen and Sam.
- 알겠습니다
- 그리고 그 유조선을 찾아
Copy that.
And find that tanker
산타모니까 부두 코 앞에서
갑자기 나타나기 전에
before it shows up 50 yards
off the Santa Monica pier.
(clicks tongue)
바빠 죽겠는데...
Ah, screw it.
(tires screeching)
이건 또 뭐야!
You idiot!
고전적인 보복 운전이죠
Classic road rage.
저거 봤어, 샘?
(sighs)
CALLEN: You see that, Sam?
SAM:
Ah...
자세히 보지 않았으면
그가 우릴 보고
You know, if I didn't
know any better,
반가워하지 않는다고
생각할 뻔 했네
I would think
he wasn't happy to see us.
자네들을 보면
항상 반갑지
Always happy to see my guys,
하지만
이 만남은
but something tells me
우연이 아니라는
확신이 있네
this meeting is
not by chance.
그 '확신'이란, 우리집
감시 카메라를 말하는거지
And by "something," I mean
my home surveillance system.
차 좋습니다
SAM:
Nice truck.
새 건가요?
Is it new?
지난번 자네들의
보스를 본 이후로
Since I last saw you and
your boss, I seem to have
나한테 '벌레(추적기)'가
들끓는 것 같아서 말이야
"bug" infestation.
차에도 달려 있고,
옷에도 달려 있고...
They're in my cars,
they're in my clothes...
새 옷장을
사야만 했다네
I had to buy a new wardrobe.
새 옷장이라,
이 옷은 합성섬유인가요?
New wardrobe.
What is this, polyester?
이집트 비단이라네
Egyptian silk.
맘에 드나?
You like?
뭐 그다지요
Not really.
물론 아니겠지
Of course not.
유럽에서 재단한거네
European cut.
어디 전쟁이라도 하러
가시나요, 아케이디?
Going to war, Arkady?
Did I not teach you anything
about being prepared?
항상 준비하고 있으라고
내가 가르치지 않았나?
왜냐하면
바주카포가 이렇게
Mm-hmm.
'Cause you never know
간편하게 나올지
몰랐거든요
when a bazooka's
gonna come in handy.
이게 뭐죠?
What is this?
오래된 싸구려
동전 같아 보이네
Looks like worthless old coin.
엘리야 버클리의
살인 사건에 대해
SAM:
What do you know
뭐 아시는 것
없나요?
about Elia Berkeley's murder?
금시 초문이네...
News to me. Uh...
그녀가 매우 힘든 달을
보내고 있는 것 같구만
Sounds like
she's having bad month.
그리고, 그녀의 동생 패트릭은
감옥에서 살해 당했습니다
Oh, and her brother Patrick
was murdered in prison
shortly after the crew
from that oil tanker
유조선 선원들 시체가
해변가로 떠밀려 온
washed up dead on the beach.
직후에 말이죠
무척 바쁜
아침 입니다
It's been a busy morning.
누군가 메시지를
보내고 있는 거라네
Somebody is sending message.
Mm-hmm.
저희와 함께 가시는게
좋을 듯 합니다
Well, maybe you better
come with us.
만일 이 일이 유조선과
관련된 반격이라면
If this is some kind of pushback
from that oil deal,
you could be next.
당신이 다음 목표가
될 수도 있어요
Sweet of you to worry,
걱정해 줘서 고맙네만,
만일 구군가 날
죽이려 하지 않는다면
but if someone
is not trying to kill me,
내가 직업에 충실하지
않았다는 얘기지
I'm not doing my job.
당신은
직업이 없습니다
You don't have a job.
자네 말은 아프구만
Your words sting,
하지만 알아,
but I know
날 생각해서 그런다는 거
it's because you care.
- 그럼 이만 난...
- 아니, 안됩니다
Now, if you'll excuse me...
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
뭐가 그렇게
급한가요?
Come on.
What's your hurry?
지난번 봤을 때는
Last time we saw you,
우리에게 보호를
요청 하셨었는데
you were begging
for our protection.
이제는 우리와 아무
상관이 없기를 바라다니요
And now you want
nothing to do with us.
개인 감정은 없네
Don't take it personally.
어쩌면 있는지도...
Or do.
어찌됐건, 난 사업상
가야할 곳이 있네
Either way,
I have business to attend to.
이 차에 실린
무기들 만으로도
Well, the weapons alone
in this truck
충분히 잡아
가둘 수 있어, 샘
are enough to bring him in, Sam.
한술 더 떠서
SAM:
Even worse,
신호 위반까지 했지
he ran a red light.
Mm-hmm.
당신 차례에요, 어르신
Your move, Big Man.
(chuckles)
동지들이랑 함께하는 시간은
항상 즐겁구만
Always nice to spend time
with comrades.
앞장 서게나
Lead the way.
에릭, 뭐 찾았어?
Eric, what do you got?
이것 좀 봐
Take a look at this.
혹시 뭐라도
건질 게 있나 싶어서
(sighs)
I initiated a search
빅터빌 형무소의
방문 시스템을
in the visitation system
at Victorville Prison,
검색하기 시작했지
see if we could catch a break.
패트릭 버클리에게
방문객이 있었거나
You know, maybe Patrick Berkeley
had a visitor,
전화온 게 있는지
or a phone call.
혹시나 해서 말이야
Shot in the dark.
뭐 나온게 있어?
Did you get any hits?
아니, 없어
No, we did not.
하지만 뭔가
이상한 걸 발견했지
But I did find something odd.
새벽 3:12 부터
3:42 사이에
Three phone calls went out
from a land line
지상전화 3통화
발신 기록이 있어
between 3:12 a.m. and 3:42 a.m.
정확히 감옥 안 어디지?
From where, exactly,
inside the prison?
3층 "D"블럭
Third floor, "D" block.
지금 그 시간대에는
Now, there's not a lot
일반 통화량이 별로 없어
of normal phone
traffic around that time.
그저 한두통의...
You know, a couple...
(clicks tongue)
음란전화나 뭐 그런 거...
...booty calls and what not.
하지만 누가 형무소에서
But who's making calls
그런 이른 새벽 시간에
that early in the morning,
지상전화로
전화를 건 걸까?
from a land line, in prison?
마티 딕스씨?
Mr. Marty Deeks?
어, 간수들?
Uh, prison personnel?
그건 그리
이상할 것도 없지
Well, that's not that odd.
간수들은 하루
3교대로 일하는데, 뭐?
Guards working third shifts
keep weird hours. So what?
좋아, 그런데 그 전화가
여기 이 주소지의
All right, but add it to the
fact that the call was placed
휴대폰으로 건 거라는
사실을 감안해 봐
to a cell phone
at this location.
아케이디의 주소네
KENSI:
That's Arkady's address.
그렇지
It is indeed.
그래서 내가 "D"블럭 내
모든 사람들의
I did a search for
everyone with access to
지상전화 접근 기록을
찾아보니
that land line in "D" Block
이 사람이
나오더군
and I came up with this guy.
챨스 터너 중사를
만나보시죠
Meet Sergeant
Charles Turner.
현재 빅터빌 형무소의
Currently a guard
at Victorville
Penitentiary.
간수야
그런데 지난
2008년에는
But back in '08,
그가 아케이디 콜첵씨의
사설 경호원으로 일 했었지
worked security for
one Mr. Arkady Kolcheck.
그게 패트릭 버클리의
암살을 사주한 사람이
This could mean Arkady's the one
아케이디임을
의미할 수도 있겠구만
that put the hit out
on Patrick Berkeley.
터너의 주소를
알고있나?
We have an address for Turner?
벌써 문자로
보내줬지
Already in your phones.
잘했어
계속 캘런과 샘에게 알려 줘
Good job. Keep Callen
and Sam in the loop.
그러지
Yep.
헤이, 선배들
NELL:
Hey, guys.
버클리 남매를 죽이려 했던
암살범에 대해서
You asked if we could find
out anything on the hit man
뭐든 좀
알아봐 달라고 하셨죠?
that tried to take
the Berkeleys out.
니콜라이 브랜토프?
Nikolai Brantov?
Unfortunately,
we did.
불행히도
뭔가를 찾았습니다
He was working as a gun
for hire, specializing in
그는 특별히
'메시지 전달자' 타입의
청부 살인 업자
였습니다
"send a message"-type contracts.
일년 전에 총기 관련 혐의로
체포 됐었습니다
He was busted a year ago
on gun charges.
누가 그를
보석 시켜줬는지 아세요?
And guess who bailed him out?
아이반 카포세프?
Ivan Karposev?
- 넵
- 이 사람은 도살꾼인데
Yep.
KENSI: This man's a butcher.
갈수록 사태가
악화 되는군
Talk about a bad day
getting worse.
카포세프가 미국에
들어와 있는지는 아나?
Do we even know if
Karposev's in the country?
아직 자세히
살펴보진 않았지만
NELL:
We haven't clocked him yet,
과도한 폭력이
사용된 것으로 보아
but given
the excessive violence,
그의 스타일이
확실합니다
it's definitely his style.
아케이디가 브랜토프를
카포세프로부터 빼내기 위해
고용한 건 아닐까?
Any chance Arkady hired Brantov
away from Karposev?
Very doubtful, Mr. Deeks.
매우 회의적이네,
딕스군
아이반 카포세프를
HETTY:
Ivan Karposev
배신 했다가는
is the kind of man
you don't double-cross
살아남지 못하네
and live to tell the tale.
카포세프는 작년에
무기거래 함정수사 때
Karposev tortured and murdered
four federal agents
네명의 연방 요원을
고문하고 죽였습니다
in a weapons trafficking
sting last year.
그는 심지어
한 요원을 시켜
He even went so far
as to force an agent
그 자신의 부하들을
염산 통 속에 빠트려
to kill his own men
by lowering them
into a vat of hydrochloric acid.
죽이기도 했습니다
이 사람은
HETTY:
The man has
전혀 인명을
중시하지 않네
no regard for life.
그러니 제군들은 항상
That's why
you'll always be
이 사람을
극히 조심해야 하네
at a disadvantage with him.
카포세프가
유조선을 쫓고 있군요
Karposev's after
the oil tanker.
궁금한 건...
I think the question is...
그가 이미 유조선을
탈취 했을까?
does he already have it?
배와 연관 된
두 명이 죽었고
Two people associated
with the ship are dead
최소한 그 중 하나는
아케이디와 연결 되어 있어
and Arkady is connected with
at least one of their murders.
맞아, 하지만
엘리야 버클리를 죽인 게
Yeah, but we don't know
if Arkady or Karposev
killed Elia Berkeley.
아케이디인지
카포세프인지 모르지
우린 카포세프가 이 일에
결부 됐는지 조차 확실히 모르고 있어
We don't even know
if Karposev is in the mix.
하지만 그가
결부 됐다면?
Yeah, but what if he is?
And he has the tanker?
그리고 유조선을
이미 탈취했다면?
Then a dangerous threat
just got more powerful.
그렇다면 훨씬 더
위험해 졌다는 얘기지
저 양반 땀 좀 나게
해 드려야 겠군
Let's let him sweat.
에릭과 넬이 아케이디와
엘리야 버클리와의
If Eric and Nell come up
with a concrete link
확실한 연결고리를
찾아 낸다면
between Arkady
and Elia Berkeley,
we'll bring the house
down on him.
아케이디는 완전히
안절부절 하겠지
내가 이 동전을 보여 줬을때
그의 반응이 어땠는지 봤어?
You see the way he reacted
when I showed him this coin?
그래, 봤지
Oh, yeah.
전부 털어 놓도록
해야겠어
I'm going to try
and run it down.
잘 해봐
I'm good.
난 이거 보고 있을께
I got this.
Wow.
간수 집 치고는 꽤 좋군
Pretty nice for a prison guard.
너도 여자들 한테
You could afford it
헤프지만 않아도
살 수 있어
if you weren't being
such a sugar daddy.
무슨 소리야?
What are you talking about?
난 내 여친을 항상
기쁘게 해 줘야 한다고
I gotta keep
my ladybird happy.
Oh, I'm not talking
about myself.
난 내 얘기
하는게 아니야
네가 친구라 부르는
빈대녀들을 말하는 거야
I am referring to the
mooch you call a friend.
꼼짝없이
걸려든 것 같은데?
Wow. Kind of walked
into that one.
- 그래 맞지?
- 저거 봤어?
Yes, you did.
See that?
KENSI:
Uh-huh.
헤이, 저거 보여?
KENSI:
Hey. See what I see?
그래, 보여
Oh, yeah.
저게 바로
'상당한 근거사유'야
That is the definition
of probable cause.
Mm-hmm.
셋에 들어간다
On three.
하나, 둘, 셋
One, two, three.
확인 끝!
DEEKS:
Clear!
확인 끝
Clear.
Wow.
터너가 여기 집에다
상자 가득히 현금를 모아놨어
Turner's got boxes
full of cash
back here, which means he either
likes to make it rain,
그 말은, 그가 돈을
비처럼 뿌리고 싶거나
아니면 부업으로 부당 이익을
취하고 있다는 얘기지
or he's hustling on the side.
딕스?
Deeks?
DEEKS:
Yeah.
터너가 재소자들에게
금지 물품 장사로
(whistles) Looks like Turner's
making a killing
톡톡한 재미를
보고 있는 모양이야
selling contraband
to the inmates.
Captive buyers.
완전 호갱들이
될 수 밖에
Supply and demand.
공급과 수요
TURNER:
Listen up!
들어라!
난 무장한 경찰이다!
I'm a cop and I'm armed!
우린 연방 요원이요
We're federal agents!
그냥 얘기 좀
나누려고요, 터너씨
We just want to talk, Turner.
(door opens, rapid footsteps)
도망가네
He's running.
- 흩어지자
- 그래
DEEKS: Split up!
Yep!
(grunting)
Ow!
딕스, 괜찮아?
Deeks, you okay?
응
Yeah.
아니, 아주 환상적이야
Ah... no, I'm fantastic.
알았어
(Deeks whoops)
KENSI: All right.
꿈꿔오던 프로 레슬링을
실제로 즐겨 본 거야?
What, are you living out your
pro wrestling fantasy? Huh?
You know,
I'd be lying
기분이 아주
끝내주지 않았다고 하면
거짓말 이겠지
if I said that
didn't feel awesome.
(sighs)
저 한테도 추적 장치를
달아 놓으셨나요, 헤티?
You have a tracking device
on me, too, Hetty?
난 단지 내 직원이
I was just wondering
무슨일로
농땡이를 피우는지
why my employee wasn't
궁금했던 것 뿐이네
on the job.
법에는 제가
점심시간 1시간과
Law requires that I take
a one-hour lunch
15분씩 두번의 휴식시간을
가져야 한다고 돼 있습니다
plus two 15 minute
breaks every day.
이게 근무 중의
점심 식사라면
Well, I'll let it slide,
이번 한번은 봐 주지
if we consider
this a working lunch.
저도 그런지
알아보는 중입니다
That is what I'm trying
to figure out.
오우, 블라디미르 레닌이군
Ooh! Vladimir Lenin.
아주 희귀한
특별판이네
Special edition.
Very rare.
주조는 됐지만
통용되진 않았지
This was minted,
but never circulated.
당시 소문에 의하면
You know it was rumored
that Lenin was
레닌은 개인 생활에서는
러시아에 비판적이었다네
critical of Russia
in his private life.
무슨 뜻이죠?
Meaning?
자네가 짐작 하는
그대로 일세
Your guess is as good as mine.
확실한건,
그게 그 사람들에게
Obviously, it meant
중요한 의미가
있었다는 거지
something to these people.
그리고 아마
자네 부친에게도 말일세
And possibly your father.
아케이디,
한스 슈라이버,
This whole thing with Arkady
그리고 제 아버지와
관련된 이 모든 건...
and Hans Schrieber
and my father, I...
아케이디는 제게 말해준 것 보다
분명 뭔가를 더 알고 있어요
Arkady knows more
than he's telling me.
제가 어디 이걸 일부러
찾으려고 했나요?
Was I meant to find this?
그 사람하고 엮이면
뭐든 가능하지
Anything's possible
with that man.
프로는 사적인 일에
휘둘리면 안되네,
Don't let the personal get in
the way of the professional,
캘런군
Mr. Callen.
그것들이 모두
하나로 뒤엉켜 있다면요?
And if they're
all wrapped up together?
그렇지 않기를
기도해야지
Pray they're not.
수고하십니다
What's up?
- 감사합니다
- 별 말씀을 요
Thanks.
No problem.
와우, 아직 못 깨어났네
Wow, he's still
out cold, huh?
그래서 만족스러워?
(laughs):
Are you gloating?
가서 그 간수한테
Listen, why don't
you go, uh, distract
네 가슴골 좀
보여주지 그래?
the guard with your cleavage?
(정말?)
(quietly):
Really?
제세동기를 써서
I'm gonna use the
defibrillator
이 친구를
깨워야 겠군
to wake him up.
그게 안 통하면
어떻게 하지?
What if
it doesn't work?
그게 무슨 소리야?
네 가슴골은 항상 통한다고
What are you talking about?
Your cleavage always works.
(chuckles)
제세동기 말이야
I was talking
about the defibrillator.
그럼 이 친군
죽겠지
Well, then he dies.
장기들을 적출해서
한 몫 잡은 후
And we harvest his organs,
make a killing,
멕시코로 튀는거지
준비 됐어?
move to Mexico. Ready?
응
Done.
(defibrillator machine whirring)
좋아, 간다!
All right. Clear!
잠깐! 하지마요
Wait! Don't.
오, 이것 좀 봐
오스카상 감이네
Oh, look at that--
and the Oscar goes to Turner.
아케이디 콜첵과
어떤 관계죠?
How do you know Arkady Kolcheck?
누구요?
Who?
그 사람 경호원을
했었잖소
Used to work security for him.
도대체 무슨 소릴
하는지 모르겠소
I don't know
what you're talking about.
- 좋아, 자 간다!
- 기다려요!
All right, clear!
Wait!
슬슬 생각이
나는게 좋을거요
KENSI: You better start
knowing, otherwise
안그러면 점프선을 연결해
기억을 되살려 줄테니까
we're gonna jump-start
your memory for you.
아케이디는 내게 돈을 주며
어떤 죄수 정보를 좀 알아봐 달라고 했소
Arkady paid me to get some
information from an inmate.
패트릭 버클리군
왜 그를 죽였죠?
Patrick Berkeley.
Why did you kill him?
난 안 죽였소
I didn't.
그저 다른 죄수 보고
I just let some
other inmates in
그를 좀 압박 해 보라고 했는데...
일이 잘못 된거요
to press him and...
it went south.
결국 당신이
죽인거 잖아
So you did kill him.
아케이디가
뭘 찾고 있었죠?
What was Arkady looking for?
이봐요, 터너,
Listen, Turner,
우린 버클리가 당신한테
뭔가를 얘기 했고,
we know that Berkeley told you
something and you called Arkady.
그 후 당신이 아케이디에게
전화한 걸 알고 있소
Hmm.
Wow.
빅터빌에서는
어느 갱이 제일 유명하죠?
Which gang is more prominent
at Victorville?
라틴 킹이던가?
Is it the Latin Kings?
맞아, 라틴 킹일거야
Yeah, I think
it's the Latin Kings.
최근에 그들이
무더기로 체포 됐었지
Remember, they got that
big bust recently?
It was, like, 50 kilos
of cocaine on the border?
국경에서 코카인
50킬로였지 아마?
맞아 맞아 맞아
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
축하해요, 터너
Congratulations, Turner.
뭘요?
On what?
이제 죄수가 되어
감옥에 가면
On your cushy new job
as the librarian
경찰에 협조 해 주신
보답으로
when you become an inmate.
편안한 도서관 일을
하게 될 테니까
You know,
for snitching to the cops.
그럴 수는 없소
You can't do that.
지켜 보시죠
Oh, watch us.
저기요...
Hey...
버클리가 당신한테
무슨 말을 했는지 말 해 주시지?
so why don't you tell us what
it is that Berkeley told you?
(defibrillator whirring)
Berkeley said
there was a backup
버클리가 어떤 배에
보조 GPS 시스템이
있다고 했소
GPS system on some ship.
그 좌표를 계속
수신하고 있는 노트북도 있고
There's a laptop
pinging its location.
어디에?
Where?
그의 누이의 집에
His sister's house.
아케이디가 그 걸 가지고 있다면
유조선이 어디 있는지도 알겠군
If Arkady has that laptop,
he knows where the tanker is.
내가 캘런과 샘에게
전화할께
I'll call Callen and Sam.
Oh, uh...
(clears his throat)
안에 가서 잘 해보쇼
good luck on the inside.
샤워장에서는 비누를
떨어뜨리면 안돼!
Don't drop that soap!
만약 엘리야가
그 노트북을 포기하지 않았고
What if Elia didn't
give up the laptop
아케이디가 그걸
찾지 못한 채 나왔다면?
and Arkady couldn't find it
before he had to bug off?
아직 그 집에 있을지도...
찾아 볼만 하겠는데?
It could still be at the house.
It's worth a shot.
노트북을 찾으면
유조선도 찾는거지
Find that laptop,
find the tanker.
다시 엘리야의 집으로...
Back to Elia's.
내가 지난번에 이 작은 방이
싫다고 했잖아
I told you last time
I hate this tiny room.
얼마나 오래 동안
내가 여기 있어야 하지?
How much longer
do I have to stay here?
당신 친구 찰스 터너에 대해서
다 말할 때 까지요
As soon as you tell me about
your buddy Charles Turner.
터너가 누구야?
Who is Turner?
형무소 간수
Prison guard.
Victorville.
빅터빌의
자넨 내가 간수들
친구로 보이나?
Do I look like I associate
with prison guards?
이 간수는 당신 휴대폰으로
전화를 걸었어요
This prison guard called
your cell phone.
잘못 건거겠지
Must've been a wrong number.
3분 22초 동안
통화를 했습니다
The call lasted
three minutes and 22 seconds.
캘런은 어디있나?
Where is Callen?
곧 올겁니다
He'll be here.
내가 지금 체포 된건가?
Am I being charged
with something?
I'm busy man.
난 바쁜 사람이라네
때가 되면
보내 드리죠
Due time, due time.
난 우리가
친구라 생각했네
I thought we were friends.
아뇨,
캘런과 제가 친구죠
No, Callen and I are friends.
그가 뭔가 과거와의
연관성 때문에
He lets you hang around
because of some ties
to the past.
당신을
놔주고 있는겁니다
You're just a source to me.
저한테 당신은 단지
정보 제공자일 뿐입니다
So if you have somewhere to be,
you're not gonna make it there
그러니 제 질문에
답하기 전에는
아무데도
못 가십니다.
unless you start
answering my questions.
알았네
Okay.
질문해 보게
Ask questions.
유조선은
어디있습니까?
Where is the oil tanker?
내가 알고있다면
자네한테 얘기 하겠지
If I knew, I would tell you.
엘리야 버클리의
노트북은 어디있나요?
Where's Elia Berkeley's laptop?
(both chuckling)
(mutters)
Hmm?
(grunts)
Yeah.
(groaning)
예전 만큼 빠르질
못하시군요, 아케이디
Not as fast as you
used to be, Arkady.
아무리 당신이라도
이건 아니죠
This is out of character,
even for you.
아주 절박한 모양이군요
You're desperate.
Tell me why.
(groaning)
왜 그런지
말해 보세요
자네는 여기서 날
내 보내줘야 하네
You need to let me
out of here.
왜 그런지 말해 봐요
Tell me why.
(grunting)
싫으면 마시던가
Suit yourself.
맘 편히 있어요
Make yourself comfortable.
여기 한 동안은
있어야 할테니까
You're gonna be here a while.
엘리야는 계속 그 석유 거래를
재개하려고 할수 밖에 없었을거야
Elia had to have been trying
to get back in on that oil deal.
그녀가 그래야만 하는 이유가
백만가지는 되겠지
Well, she's got a hundred
million reasons to try.
그녀는 분명 그들이
쫓아오고 있다는 걸
And she obviously didn't know
they were coming after her
or she would've
gone into hiding.
혹은 어딘가로
숨어야 한다는 걸 몰랐어
Clearly the Berkeleys
didn't know
확실히
버클리 남매는
그들의 거래 상대에 대해
몰랐던 거야
who they were getting
in bed with.
켄지!
Kens!
엎드려!
Get down!
괜찮아?
You okay?
(groans, laughs)
부딪힌 것 보다
귀가 더 아프네
My bruises are gonna heal
faster than my hearing.
그놈 맞혔어?
Did you hit him?
어깨를 맞힌 것 같아
Yeah, I think I winged him.
번호판이
없는 차였어
Car didn't have
any plates on it.
(groans)
어깨를 맞힌 것 같고,
차는...
(loudly): I said I think
I winged him; the car...
알아, 들었어!
Yeah, I heard you!
Okay, you don't have to,
you don't have to yell about it.
알았어, 그렇게
소리 안 질러도 돼
My ears are fine.
내 귀는 괜찮거든
(door closes)
아케이디가
손들었나?
Arkady give up anything?
그가 내게
주먹을 휘둘렀어
He took a swing at me.
뭐라고?
What?!
그게 믿어져?
Can you believe that?
(laughs)
그 나이에
제법 빠르더군
He's pretty spry
for an old guy.
뭘 어쩌겠나?
What you gonna do?
아케이디가
시간에 쫓기는게 확실 해
I have the distinct feeling that
Arkady's running out of time.
(computer chirps)
선배님들
Hey, guys.
뭐 좀 알아냈나,
에릭?
What do you have, Eric?
아케이디의
영상인데
Footage of Arkady outside
엘리야 버클리의 집 밖에서
오늘아침 찍힌겁니다
of Elia Berkeley's house
this morning.
동네의 모든 CCTV 영상을
긁어 모으는데
시간이 좀 걸렸습니다
Took me a while to round up all
the neighbor's security footage.
고맙네, 에릭
Thank you, Eric.
별 말씀을요
My pleasure.
이런말 하긴 싫지만
Hate to say it,
but it looks like
아무래도 아케이디가 패트릭과
엘리야 버클리를 죽인것으로 보이네
Arkady took out
Patrick and Elia Berkeley.
아케이디는
중개상이야
Arkady's a broker.
그는 구매자도
판매자도 아니지
He's not a buyer or a seller.
어쩌면 그가 계약을
원래대로 되돌리려 해서
Maybe he was trying
to put the deal back together,
and someone got
to the Berkeleys first.
누군가를 시켜 버클리를
우선 처리 한건지도 몰라
The same person
who T-boned Kensi and Deeks?
켄지와 딕스를 들이받은
바로 그 놈이겠지
It's got to be Karposev.
그게 카포세프일까?
아케이디는 여기서 발 빼는데
왜 그렇게 필사적일까?
Why would Arkady be so desperate
to get out of here?
그냥 편히 앉아서
He could just kick back,
우리가 카포세프를
처리 하도록
그냥 둬도 되잖아
let us take care of Karposev.
There's got
to be another reason.
무슨 다른 이유가 있겠지
자넨 내 의지에 반해서
나를 구금하고 있네
You're holding me
against my will.
This is not legal.
그건 불법이지
살인 용의자를 구금하는건
엄청 합법이죠
Holding a murder suspect
is plenty legal.
살인?
무슨 살인?
Murder? What murder?
하나가 아니죠
페트릭과 엘리야 버클리
No, not just one--
Patrick and Elia Berkeley.
형무서 간수가 죄수를
죽이는 일은 흔한 일이지
Prison guards kill inmates
all the time.
나와는 전혀
상관 없는 일이네
Had nothing
to do with me.
엘리야 언급은
피하시는 군요
Doesn't explain Elia.
당신이
그녀가 죽기전
We have footage
그녀 집 바깥에서 찍힌
CCTV 영상이 있습니다
placing you outside her house
before she was murdered.
그녀는 내가 거기 갔다가
나올때까지 살아 있었네
Elia was alive when I got there,
and when I left.
노트북
어디있습니까?
Where's the laptop?
안에 뭐가 들었는지도
말 해주면 금상첨화죠
Better yet, what's on it?
You working with Ivan Karposev?
아이반 카포세프와
함께 일하나요?
I thought you guys were supposed
to be smart.
난 자네들이
똑똑한 줄 알았는데?
그럼 저희를 좀
깨우쳐 주시죠?
Then why don't you enlighten us?
You want the tanker?
그 유조선을 원하나?
어디 있는지
아시는군요
Oh, you know where to find it.
GPS 좌표라네
GPS location.
확인해 보겠습니다
I'll verify it.
우린 지금
시간 낭비를 하고있네
We're wasting time.
이게 뭔지 알고계시죠?
I know you know what that is.
한스 슈라이버로 부터
받아서 저에게 주신
I saw the same image
on the clippings you gave me
from Hans Schrieber.
신문기사 스크랩들 중에서
똑같은 모양을 봤습니다
러시아로부터
탈출하고 싶어하는
난민들을 구별하기 위해
We use these coins
to identify refugees wanting
우린 이 동전을
이용 한다네
to escape from Russia.
그들이 동전을
내게 건네주면
They would
hand them to me...
그들을 믿을 수 있게
되는거지
...and I knew
I could trust them.
난민들에게는
누가 동전을 주나요?
Who gave the refugees the coins?
반대쪽에 있는
그 사람이
The man on the other end.
My father?
제 아버지인가요?
Possibly.
아마 그럴지도
확실히 말해 줄 수는
없네, 캘런
But I cannot say
for sure, Callen.
엘리야 버클리는
어떻게 된 건가요?
What happened to
Elia Berkeley?
카포세프는 석유 거래에
어떤 골칫거리라도 생기는 걸
원치 않았네
Karposev didn't want any
complications with the oil sale.
슬프게도 엘리야가
그 골칫거리 였지
Sadly, Elia was
a complication.
당신은요?
And what about you?
카포세프는
날 건드리지 못해
Karposev cannot touch me.
날 살려 둬야 유리하지
Benefits of being connected.
당신이
카포세프에게
Prove to me
이 모든 걸 뒤집어 씌우려는 게
아니라는 걸 증명해 보세요
that you're not just trying
to pin all this Karposev.
그 배 선원 중에
내 동료가 하나 있네
I have an associate on the crew.
내 전화를
조사해 봐
Check my phone.
그 아가씨 기억하나?
Remember the girl?
애나
Anna.
아나
맞아
Yes.
카포세프가
동영상을 보내왔네
Karposev sent a video.
그녀는 지금
위험에 처했어
She's in danger.
이 여자는 당신이 이렇게
위험을 자초할 만큼
Well, this associate must
be pretty important
for you to stick
your neck out like this.
당신한테 꽤
중요한 모양이군요
I am loyal to the people
who work for me.
나는 나를 위해 일하는
사람들에게 매우 충실하다네
그럴리가요
I don't buy it.
사실이야
It is true.
선배들 괜찮아요?
You guys all right?
아직 멀쩡하지
Still in one piece.
누가 LAPD에
총격사건 제보를 했어요
Okay, LAPD got a call
about a shooting.
잠깐만
DEEKS:
Wait a minute.
저거 우릴 들이받았던
그 차 아냐?
Isn't that the car
that rammed us?
아이반 카포세프네
There's Ivan Karposev.
악마같은 놈
DEEKS:
The Devil himself.
저기 어깨를 봐...
내가 맞힌거 맞네
Look at this shoulder--
I knew I winged him.
설마 저놈이...
DEEKS:
Tell me he's not gonna...
Mm-hmm.
(clears throat)
저 사람이 노트북을
찾아 왔어야 했는데
못 그랬나 봐
That guy was supposed to find
the laptop and didn't deliver.
빈손으로 돌아오면
저런 일이 생기는거야
This is what happens when you
come back empty-handed.
아케이디가
엘리야를 죽인게 아니네
KENSI:
Arkady didn't kill Elia.
카포세프가
죽인거야
Karposev did.
제가 선배들한테
전화 할께요
I'll call the guys.
(anxious gasping)
CALLEN:
He's telling the truth.
그는 진실을
말하고 있어
그녀의 이름은
애나야
Her name's Anna.
아케이디가
엘리야를 죽인게 아니라면
If Arkady didn't kill Elia,
he probably didn't kill
Patrick, either.
패트릭을 죽이지도
않았겠군
So I triple-checked Arkady's
GPS coordinates--
제가 아케이디가 준 GPS 좌표를
세번이나 재 확인 해 봤는데
거긴 사하라 사막
한 가운데 입니다
it's the middle
of the Sahara Desert.
우릴 갖고
놀고있어
He's playing us.
우릴 갖고 놀기엔
그는 지금 너무 절박해
No, he's too desperate
to play us.
거래를
하자는거군
He's bargaining.
뭔가 댓가를
바라는 거야
He wants something in return.
그게 뭔지를
알아볼 시간이군
It's time to find out
what it is.
거 참 재밌게도
It's funny...
유조선 좌표라고
준 곳이
coordinates you
gave us put the tanker
사하라 사막
한 가운데 더군요
in the middle of
the Sahara Desert.
잘못 읽었겠지
Must have been typo.
다시 해 보게
Try again.
이번엔
잘 써 봐요
No typos this time.
날 데려가 준다면
No typos...
잘 써 보지...
if you take me with you.
자네가 카포세프를
찾을때 쯤이면
By the time
you find Karposev,
그는 석유를 모두 하역하고
이미 사라져 버렸을꺼야
he will have unloaded the oil,
and he will be gone.
당신 동료와
함께겠죠
And your associate with him.
그렇게 둬선
안돼지
Does not have to be this way.
거래 하겠나?
Deal?
좋습니다
Deal.
약속 한거지?
I have your word?
그냥 저희를
믿으시면 됩니다
You just have to trust us.
Okay.
Let's do this.
좋아, 해 보자고
이리로 오게
Come on.
말씀만 하세요,
준비 됐습니다
ERIC:
Ready when you are.
위도 33.4
Latitude: 33.4.
경도 118.2
Longitude: 118.2.
저긴
샌피드로인데
That's San Pedro.
배는 아직
LA 항구에 있어
Ship's still in port, in L.A.
이분은 여기
남아 있어야 합니다
He stays with the truck.
We had deal.
거래를 했잖은가
The deal was we bring you with us.
And we did.
거래는 당신을 여기 함께
데려오는거 까지 였죠
Now the deal is you stay here.
Let's move.
그러니 여기 계세요
가자!
하나, 둘, 셋
One, two, three.
나머지
선원들이겠군
KENSI: Must be
the remaining crew members.
딕스, 1억불 어치 석유면
백만통은 되겠지?
Deeks, $100 million in oil is
about a million barrels, right?
계산기는 안 가져왔지만
에릭과 넬에 의하면
I mean, I don't have
my Acme oil converter,
대략 그정도
맞을꺼야
but according to Eric and Nell,
yeah, that's about right.
여기 겨우
97통 밖에 없어
KENSI: There's only
97 barrels here.
우리가 너무
늦었단 얘기군
That means
we're too late.
캘런, 샘 선배, 카포세프가
이미 석유를 옮겼어요
Callen, Sam, Karposev's
already moved the oil.
총이다!
Shooter!
흩어지자
DEEKS:
Split up.
엎드려!
DEEKS:
Down!
(man groans)
꼼짝말고
KENSI:
Stay down.
엎어져있어
자 이제
돌아 누워
Let's go!
Turn over.
수갑 채웠어, 켄지
I got him, Kens.
딕스!
Deeks!
왜?
Yeah?
여기 폭탄이
설치 됐어
This place is rigged to blow.
시간이 얼마나
남았는데?
How much time?
타이머가 안보여
I don't see a timer.
기폭장치를 아직
설치하지 않았어
They haven't set
a detonator, yet.
좋아, 이놈을
캘런과 샘에게 데려 가자고
All right, let's get him
to Sam and Callen now.
(man grunts, groans)
확인 끝
Clear.
What you mean, "clear"?
무슨소리야,
'확인 끝'이라니?
거의 쏠 뻔 했어요
You almost got yourself shot.
트럭 옆에 있으라고
했잖습니까
We told you
to stay in the truck.
경비원은
어디갔죠?
Where's the guard?
늙긴 했지만
아직은 꽤 빠르다네
I'm still plenty fast
for old man.
캘런, 샘 선배,
우리 지금 들어갑니다
KENSI (over radio):
Callen, Sam, we're coming in.
이놈은 누구야?
Who's this?
배에 폭탄 설치 중인 걸
잡았습니다
We found him rigging
the ship to blow.
앉아
Get down.
나머지 선원들은
어디갔지?
Where is rest
of crew?
우리가 여기 도착하기 전에
카포세프가 그들을 처치 했습니다
Karposev got to them
before we got here.
Was there woman?
No, there was no woman.
- 여자가 있었나?
- 아니, 여자는 없었습니다
저 양반 여기서
뭐하는 거죠?
W-What is he doing here?
Told him
to wait in the car.
차에 남아 있으라고
했었어
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, hey.
그녀는 어디있지?
나의 아나는 어디있냐고!
Where is she?!
Where is my Anna?!
'나의 아나'라니,
무슨 얘기죠?
What do you mean
"your Anna"?
당신 딸이로군요
She's your daughter.
그렇다네, 캘런
Yes, Callen.
내 딸이야
She is my daughter.
이놈은 내 딸이
어디있는지 알고있어
And this man knows
where she is.
카포세프는
어디있나?
SAM:
Where's Karposev?
그 여자는
어디있지?
Where's the girl?
좋아
Fine.
맘대로 하세요, 아케이디
우린 가자
He's all yours,
Arkady.
Let's go.
Wait, wait, wait!
잠 잠 잠깐만!
카포세프가 그녀를
데려 갔습니다
Karposev took her with him.
어디로?
Where?
러시아로
To Russia.
거기가 석유 경매가
이뤄지는 곳입니다
That's where the auction
for the oil's taking place.
석유는 지금
어디있지?
Where is the oil now?
이미 떠났습니다
It's gone.
해상에서
작은 유조선 3척에
We off-loaded
most of it
onto three smaller
tankers, out at sea.
대부분을 모두
나눠 실었습니다
절대로
못 찾을겁니다
(laughing):
You'll never find them.
배들에는 절대
깃발을 꽂지 않기때문에
The ships were
never flagged.
배가 어디에서 왔는지,
어디로 가는지 알 수가 없죠
Don't know where they're from,
where they're going.
그러면 유조선은 왜
LA로 다시 갖다놨지?
So why'd you bring
the ship back to L.A.?
나머지 석유는
어디있고?
Where's the rest
of the oil?
The cartels bought the rest.
조직들이 나머지를
샀습니다
우린 배를 다시 출항시켜
바다 한가운데서
We were set to
sail the ship
우리가 보관중인 석유와 함께
폭파 시키려고 했습니다
back to sea and blow it
with the oil we kept.
그러면 사람들이 그 석유가
배와 함께 폭파 되었다고
생각할 테니까요
And the world thinks
the oil blew with it.
Makes for an easier sell.
팔기 쉽도록
꾸미는 거네
Karposev sells that oil
for $100 million,
카포세프는 그 석유를
1억 달라에 파니까
그는 더욱 위협적인
존재가 되는거지
he becomes a next-level threat.
My contacts in Russia
can track Karposev,
내 러시아
연락책을 통해
카포세프를
추적해 보겠네
if only...
만일... 자네가 내 딸 아나를
찾는걸 도와 준다면 말이지
you help me find
my daughter Anna.
난 안 내켜
I don't like it.
아케이디의 연락책이 어쩌면
카포세프를 잡을 수 있는
최선의 방법일지도 몰라
Arkady's contacts may be our
best shot at getting Karposev.
Okay.
좋아
애나를 찾고, 카포세프를 찾아서
거래를 중단 시켜야지
Find Anna, we find Karposev,
stop the sale.
인정하긴 싫지만
I hate to admit it,
우린 그가 필요해
but we need him.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
[ 다음편에 계속... ]
자네가 보드카를 좋아하길 바래
CALLEN:
I hope you like vodka.